

## ABOUT ME

I'm an organized and responsible person, always open to improvement.

In my last years of high school I gained work experience by participating in different ventures and I was distinguished as "Hope of the Homeland 2022".

Autonomously I improved and expanded my computer skills and I'm interested in further training in accounting, financial and administrative issues, and in ERP's and other similar software tools.



[♀*=*] **46.418.935** 





Unmarried



CONTACT



marcos\_lorenzana@hotmail.com



+54 9 11 3762-3202



www.gabyxer.com



Lomas del Mirador, La Matanza, Province of Buenos Aires, Argentina.

**COMPUTER SKILLS / TOOLS** 

#### Basic Level

## Intermediate Level

- Photoshop

- Excel
- Visual Studio Code

# MARCOS GABRIEL LORENZANA

PUBLIC ACCOUNTANT STUDENT

## **ACADEMIC TRAINING**

#### National University of La Matanza

Degree Course: Public Accountant, 2023 - in progress

#### San José Obrero Institute

Bachelor in Economics and Administration, 2017 - 2022

- Academic average 9.37
- Distinction "Hope of the Homeland 2022"

## **WORK EXPERIENCE**

## **Head of Administration and Finance** Emparedadon't, July 2022 - November 2022

- Preparation of formal and commercial documentation of the company.
- · Compilation and registration of legal and management information.
- · Elaboration and control of the budget.
- · Cost calculation.
- Administration of economic resources.
- · Planning and monitoring of collections and control of discounts.

## Temporary Manager

Futuros Inflables, November 3, 2022

- · Preparation of tickets.
- Supervision of the inflatable.
- · Customer care.

# Accounting Management Manager

Sanjo Sabores, October 2021 - November 2021

- Preparation of formal and commercial documentation of the company.
- · Registration of operations.
- · Funds management.

## **LANGUAGES**

